https://worthyministries.com/privacy-policy/

Statement of Faith
What is a Christian?
Bible
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our network of websites: Worthy Ministries, Worthy Network, Worthy News, Worthy Devotions, Worthy Christian Forums, Worthy Christian Chat, Worthy Prayer Team, Worthy.Bible, Worthy Brief, Worthy Email, Worthy Christian Search, Worthy Christian Library, Worthy Hosting,  Worthy Plugins, Christian Persecution.Info, and Prophecy News Watch.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on February 4, 2019
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Worthy Ministries
106 Sheffield Place
Franklin, TN 37067-4437
USA
Sign Up for our Worthy Briefs!
We guarantee 100% privacy.
Your information will not be shared.
Email Address
First Name
Last Name
We use MailChimp as our email list platform. By clicking below to submit this form, you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms.
Be sure to check your SPAM box and whitelist our emails to ensure delivery!
Latest Worthy BriefsWorthy Brief - 12/10/2020Worthy Brief - 12/9/2020Worthy Brief - 12/8/2020Worthy Brief - 12/7/2020Worthy Brief - 12/4/2020Worthy Brief - 12/3/2020Worthy Brief - 12/2/2020Worthy Brief - 12/1/2020Worthy Brief - 11/30/2020Worthy Brief - 11/27/2020Connect with us!
Worthy Ministries
Worthy Brief
Worthy Christian Books
Worthy Hosting
Worthy Plugins
Worthy Israel Tours
Worthy Christian Comics
Worthy Christian Search
What is a Christian?
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.Ok
